

ABOUT ME

I'm a geo and full stack developer based in Bermejo, BO specializing in building (and occasionally designing) amazing websites, apps, and everything in between, passionate about technologies and love to learn new things.

I'm a Padawan Community Ambassador of Hackademy, Mexico

I currently work (remote) as a Full Stack Developer for Bluebamboo, Argentina

CONTACTS

- +591 72900865
- ✓ d.cruz@outlook.com
- doctsystems.github.io
- Topater esq. German Busch Bermejo, Bolivia.

SKILLS

Python, Django

Geodjango

Leaflet

Git, Github

INTEREST













CRUZ DIEGO OSVALDO

Geo and Web Developer

EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER 2020 - Present

BLUEBAMBOO

- Backend development of the MESi Project of the Interdisciplinary Institute of Political Economy of Buenos Aires (IIEP)
- Web development of the AFISPOP Project, IIEP Fiscal Studies and Public Policies Area
- Backend and Frontend of the ICCI Project, Insertion, Trade and International Competitiveness

 Area
- Regional I-O MATRIX, González, S. N., Romero, C. A., Negri, P. A., Ramos, M. P., & Marino, M. (2020).
 Regional Input-Output Tables Estimation through Indirect Methods

JUNIOR PRODUCT MANAGER 2017 - 2020

DOCTSYSTEMS

- Manage the work of developers. Detect new needs of our clients, analyze them and decide how they are done.
- Study the evolution of software development.
- Establish working methods within the technical area.

IT DEPARTMENT MANAGER 2013 - 2017

GOVERNORATE OF BERMEJO

- Support and Training in Administrative System (Sales, Accounting and Production). Detect technical failures of equipment.
- Scheduled maintenance and configuration of user equipment, networks and servers.
- Development of customized systems. Support and Training in systems management.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY 2006 - 2011

UNIVERSIDAD PRIVADA DOMINGO SAVIO

Systems Engineer

INSTITUTE 2003 - 2005

INSTITUTO TECNICO DOMINGO SAVIO

Computer Support and Maintenance Technician

HIGHSCHOOL 1999 - 2002 OCTAVIO CAMPERO ECHAZU